{"name": "E25 2022-4", "questions": [{"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "1. The table below gives the exact probability of randomly drawing a marble of a particular color from a bag of solid-colored marbles.What is the probability of randomly drawing a marble that is NOT green and is NOT blue?", "choices": {"A": "0.60", "B": "0.63", "C": "0.67", "D": "0.70", "E": "0.90"}, "correct": "A"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "2. What is the value of x in the equation  ?", "choices": {"A": "", "B": "", "C": "", "D": "", "E": "2"}, "correct": "B"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "3. (3a6b) (7a3b9) is equivalent to:", "choices": {"A": "10a9b10", "B": "10a18b9", "C": "21a9b9", "D": "21a9b10", "E": "21a18b9"}, "correct": "D"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "4. During the month of July, Garth's Video tracked the number of videos rented for each transaction. A total of 600 transactions were made during the month of July. The results are shown in the table below. How many transactions of exactly 3 video rentals were made during the month of July?", "choices": {"A": "48", "B": "120", "C": "156", "D": "216", "E": "336"}, "correct": "C"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "5. The total price for the pizza Jana and her friends bought was $15.60. The pizza was cut into 8 equal slices, and Jana ate 3 of the slices. Jana paid a portion of the total price that was the same as the portion of the pizza she ate. What portion of the total price did Jana pay?", "choices": {"A": "$1.95", "B": "$4.68", "C": "$5.20", "D": "$5.85", "E": "$7.80"}, "correct": "D"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "6. If f(x) = (5x + 3)2, then f(1) = ?", "choices": {"A": "8", "B": "16", "C": "28", "D": "34", "E": "64"}, "correct": "E"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "7. The mean of 4 numbers is 6. Given that 3 of the numbers are 3, 6, and 7, what is the remaining number?", "choices": {"A": "2", "B": "", "C": "4", "D": "8", "E": "16"}, "correct": "D"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "8. The midpoint of NQ is located at M(3,5) in the standard (x,y) coordinate plane. Given that the coordinates of Q are (1,2), what are the coordinates of N ?", "choices": {"A": "(1, )", "B": "(2, )", "C": "(5, 8)", "D": "(5, 12)", "E": "(7, 12)"}, "correct": "C"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "9. What is the value of |-3| - |7 - 49| \uff1f", "choices": {"A": "-45", "B": "-39", "C": "39", "D": "45", "E": "59"}, "correct": "B"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "10. Australia's Sydney Opera House covers a rectangular region that has a length of 605 feet and a width of 388 feet. Which of the following values is closest to the area, in acres, of the rectangular region?(Note: 1 acre = 43,560 square feet)", "choices": {"A": "5", "B": "70", "C": "110", "D": "68,000", "E": "230,000"}, "correct": "A"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "11. 52x-2y47-1 is equivalent to:", "choices": {"A": "", "B": "", "C": "", "D": "", "E": ""}, "correct": "B"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "12. The lengths of the 2 shorter sides of a right triangle are 2 cm and 3 cm, respectively. Which of the following values is closest to the length, in centimeters, of the longest side of the triangle?", "choices": {"A": "2.2", "B": "2.3", "C": "3.6", "D": "5.0", "E": "6.5"}, "correct": "C"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "13. When y = x and x + y = 10 are graphed in the standard (x,y) coordinate plane, at what point do they intersect?", "choices": {"A": "(-5,5)", "B": "(0,10)", "C": "(5,-5)", "D": "(5,5)", "E": "(10,0)"}, "correct": "D"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "14. The first 4 terms of a geometric sequence are listed in order below. What is the seventh term of the sequence?                                                          24, 12, 6, 3, \u00b7\u00b7\u00b7", "choices": {"A": "-6", "B": "0", "C": "0.1875", "D": "0.375", "E": "0.75"}, "correct": "D"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "15. Let s be any real number such that 4 &lt;  &lt; 9. Which of the following is a possible value of s ?", "choices": {"A": "2.5", "B": "7.6", "C": "12.7", "D": "39.3", "E": "82.4"}, "correct": "D"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "16. In the standard (x,y) coordinate plane, which of the following lines goes through (0,2) and is parallel to y = -5x + 7?", "choices": {"A": "y = -5x - 2", "B": "y = -5x + 2", "C": "y = x - 2", "D": "y = x + 2", "E": "y = 2x + 7"}, "correct": "B"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "17. What is the slope of the line in the standard (x,y) coordinate plane that contains the points (6,-1) and (4,3) ?", "choices": {"A": "-2", "B": "-1", "C": "", "D": "", "E": "5"}, "correct": "A"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "18. If 8y = 3x - 5, then x = ?", "choices": {"A": "y + 5", "B": "y - 5", "C": "y + 5", "D": "", "E": ""}, "correct": "E"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "19. A tank has a capacity of 30 gallons and is  full of water. Jamal then removes of the water in the tank. How many gallons of water are left in the tank?", "choices": {"A": "", "B": "5", "C": "", "D": "", "E": ""}, "correct": "D"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "20. Which of the following expressions is equivalent to 3(a + b) - 5(a - 2b) ?", "choices": {"A": "-2a - 9b", "B": "-2a - 7b", "C": "-2a - b", "D": "-2a + 5b", "E": "-2a + 13b"}, "correct": "E"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "21. An English teacher decided to give a second test over the same material as a first test. To reward those students who did well and to provide an incentive to students to improve their score, he announced that he would calculate the combined test score by starting with the first test score and adding of the increase in test score from their first test to their second test. Trish scored 57 points on her first test and 72 points on her second test. What is her combined test score?", "choices": {"A": "62", "B": "67", "C": "72", "D": "82", "E": "95"}, "correct": "B"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "22. Which of the following expressions is equal to  \uff1f", "choices": {"A": "2", "B": "8", "C": "", "D": "", "E": ""}, "correct": "C"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "23. On a rectangular sheet of paper, Aiko drew a triangle whose base length is the same as the length of the sheet and whose height is the same as the width of the sheet. What is the ratio of the area of the triangle to the area of the rectangular sheet of paper?", "choices": {"A": "", "B": "", "C": "", "D": "1", "E": "2"}, "correct": "C"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "24. Norah invited 4 friends to a table tennis party. Each of the 5 people at the party played every other person exactly 1 time. The table below shows the number of games won by each player except Norah. There were no ties. How many games did Norah win?", "choices": {"A": "0", "B": "1", "C": "2", "D": "3", "E": "4"}, "correct": "D"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "25. A parallelogram has a perimeter of 80 inches, and 1 of its sides measures 18 inches. If it can be determined, what are the lengths, in inches, of the other 3 sides?", "choices": {"A": "18, 18, 26", "B": "18, 13, 13", "C": "18, 22, 22", "D": "18, 31, 31", "E": "Cannot be determined from the given information"}, "correct": "C"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "26. Use the following information to answer 26-28.The 2010 ADA Standards for Accessible Design require that elevator cars with centered doors, like the one shown below, have a minimum door clear width of 42 inches. They also require a minimum number of wheelchair spaces in 1 assembly area, such as a classroom, based on the number of seats in the assembly area, as the table below indicates.26. Door clear widths in feet. of 5 elevator cars with centered doors built before 2010 are listed below.             3.5, 3.6, 3.8, 3.2, 2.8How many of the elevator cars do NOT meet the 2010 ADA standard for minimum door clear width?", "choices": {"A": "1", "B": "2", "C": "3", "D": "4", "E": "5"}, "correct": "B"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "27. Use the following information to answer 26-28.The 2010 ADA Standards for Accessible Design require that elevator cars with centered doors, like the one shown below, have a minimum door clear width of 42 inches. They also require a minimum number of wheelchair spaces in 1 assembly area, such as a classroom, based on the number of seats in the assembly area, as the table below indicates.27. An elevator car with centered doors has a door clear width that is 8% wider than the minimum distance required by the 2010 ADA standard. Which of the following distances, in inches, is closest to the door clear width of the elevator car?", "choices": {"A": "43", "B": "45", "C": "50", "D": "62", "E": "76"}, "correct": "B"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "28. Use the following information to answer 26-28.The 2010 ADA Standards for Accessible Design require that elevator cars with centered doors, like the one shown below, have a minimum door clear width of 42 inches. They also require a minimum number of wheelchair spaces in 1 assembly area, such as a classroom, based on the number of seats in the assembly area, as the table below indicates.28. A local college will construct a 2-floor building next year. Each of the 5 classrooms on the 1st floor will have 20 seats, and each of the 8 classrooms on the 2nd floor will have 35 seats. To comply with the 2010 ADA standard, what is the fewest total number of wheelchair spaces needed in the 13 classrooms?", "choices": {"A": "4", "B": "6", "C": "11", "D": "13", "E": "21"}, "correct": "E"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "29. A paint researcher collected the following data about the relationship between the paint level in a paint can and the surface area painted from this can.Assume there is a linear relationship between x and y. Which of the following is an equation showing this relationship?", "choices": {"A": "y = 32x", "B": "y = x + 96", "C": "y = x + 32", "D": "x = 32y", "E": ""}, "correct": "A"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "30. Which of the following sentences is true about the 2 nonright angles of any right triangle?", "choices": {"A": "They are complementary angles.", "B": "They are congruent angles.", "C": "They are obtuse angles.", "D": "They are supplementary angles.", "E": "They are vertical angles."}, "correct": "A"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "31. The temperature in Chicago was -4\u00b0F at noon and rose 24\u00b0F by 3:00 p.m. The temperature in New Orleans was 42\u00b0F at noon and dropped 24\u00b0F by 3:00 p.m. How did the temperatures in Chicago and New Orleans compare at 3:00 p.m. ?", "choices": {"A": "New Orleans was 10\u00b0F colder than Chicago.", "B": "New Orleans was 2\u00b0F colder than Chicago.", "C": "The temperatures were the same.", "D": "New Orleans was 22\u00b0F warmer than Chicago.", "E": "New Orleans was 46\u00b0F warmer than Chicago."}, "correct": "B"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "32. In the figure below,  and  intersect at O, bisects \u2220BOD, and the measure of \u2220AOD is 40\u00b0. What is the measure of \u2220AOE?", "choices": {"A": "40\u00b0", "B": "50\u00b0", "C": "60\u00b0", "D": "70\u00b0", "E": "80\u00b0"}, "correct": "D"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "33. The entire length of a rope is coiled into 6 circular loops, each with a diameter of 10 inches, as shown below. Which of the following is closest to the length, in inches, of the rope?", "choices": {"A": "30", "B": "80", "C": "95", "D": "190", "E": "315"}, "correct": "D"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "34. Given the matrix equation below, what is the value of ab?", "choices": {"A": "-40", "B": "-3", "C": "-2", "D": "", "E": ""}, "correct": "A"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "35. In right triangle \u25b3ABC, the right angle is at B, and sin A = .  What is the value of tan C?", "choices": {"A": "", "B": "", "C": "", "D": "", "E": ""}, "correct": "A"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "36. During rehearsal for the Founders\u2018 Day choir program, the director, Mrs. Mazurek, tried 3 different configurations, each using all the choir members at the rehearsal. One configuration was to have only rows of 12, one was to have only rows of 15, and one was to have only rows of 20. None of these configurations worked because for each, the last row had 1 person less than the other rows. What was the least of the possible numbers of choir members at the rehearsal?", "choices": {"A": "44", "B": "47", "C": "59", "D": "79", "E": "119"}, "correct": "C"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "37. The equation x2 + P = 0, where P is an integer, has 2 integer solutions for x. Which of the following is a possible value of P?", "choices": {"A": "-48", "B": "-36", "C": "-10", "D": "36", "E": "48"}, "correct": "B"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "38. Of the 17 members of Xavier High School's honor society, 1 member will be chosen at random to attend a conference. The table below shows the number of honor society members according to class and whether they are in their first or second year in the honor society. What is the probability that the member chosen will NOT be a senior who is in his or her second year in the honor society?", "choices": {"A": "", "B": "", "C": "", "D": "", "E": ""}, "correct": "D"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "39. Given x = 4y and y = 22, which of the following expressions is equivalent to x + 4y - 8z in terms of z?", "choices": {"A": "-3z", "B": "-2z", "C": "2z", "D": "4z", "E": "8z"}, "correct": "E"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "40. Using the street map shown below, you are directed to take a 4-block-long route to walk from First and Main Streets to Third and Market Streets. If each of the different 4-block-long routes consists of a unique sequence of streets, how many such routes could you take?", "choices": {"A": "4", "B": "6", "C": "8", "D": "12", "E": "16"}, "correct": "B"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "41. For i = , (3 + i)2 = ?", "choices": {"A": "-9", "B": "8", "C": "8 + 6i", "D": "6 + i", "E": "6 + 2i"}, "correct": "C"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "42. Define the functions f(x) and g(x) such that f(x) = 2x and g(x) = . For all x such that x \u2265 -3, which of the following expressions is equal to f(g(x))?", "choices": {"A": "", "B": "", "C": "", "D": "", "E": ""}, "correct": "A"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "43. In a small high school with 20 seniors, 8 of the seniors are in soccer, 9 of the seniors are in band, and 5 of the seniors are in both. How many seniors are in neither soccer nor band?", "choices": {"A": "15", "B": "12", "C": "11", "D": "8", "E": "3"}, "correct": "D"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "44. For any real number x such that x &lt; -5 in the equation below, which of the following statements must be true of the number represented by y ?       ", "choices": {"A": "y is irrational.", "B": "y \uff1e 0", "C": "y = 0", "D": "y \uff1c 0", "E": "y is imaginary."}, "correct": "E"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "45. The population of North town onJanuary 1 for the years 2001 through 2007 is shown in the table below. What is the average yearly change in population from January 1, 2003, to January 1, 2005 ?   ", "choices": {"A": "82", "B": "120", "C": "123", "D": "124", "E": "246"}, "correct": "C"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "46. The bottom of the empty rectangular storage bin shown below is a square. If 175 cubic feet of salt are poured into the bin and leveled. how many feet of the bin will be filled?", "choices": {"A": "7", "B": "17.5", "C": "25", "D": "35", "E": "That much salt will more than fill the bin."}, "correct": "A"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "47. One of the following graphs is the graph of y \u2264 ax + b for some positive a and positive b. Which graph?", "choices": {"A": "", "B": "", "C": "", "D": "", "E": ""}, "correct": "A"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "48. The ratings from a survey taken by 90 students are summarized in the frequency bar graph below. The possible ratings on the survey are 0, 1, 2, 3, and 4.", "choices": {"A": "2", "B": "", "C": "", "D": "", "E": "3"}, "correct": "B"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "49. A vote revealed that chocolate ice cream was favored by more students in Hillhouse High School than any other flavor of ice cream. Which of the following statistical measures was most likely used to determine this result?", "choices": {"A": "Mean", "B": "Median", "C": "Mode", "D": "Range", "E": "Variance"}, "correct": "C"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "50. Use the following information to answer questions 50-52.Harold is planning a garden as shown in the scale drawing below. The line segments represent the fence surrounding the garden, with an opening in the fence to access the garden. Each small square in the scale drawing represents a square with a side length of 2 feet. Each marked point is at the vertex of a small square in the drawing.50.  What will be the length, in feet, of the fence surrounding Harold's garden?", "choices": {"A": "26", "B": "28", "C": "52", "D": "56", "E": "60"}, "correct": "C"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "51. Use the following information to answer questions 50-52.Harold is planning a garden as shown in the scale drawing below. The line segments represent the fence surrounding the garden, with an opening in the fence to access the garden. Each small square in the scale drawing represents a square with a side length of 2 feet. Each marked point is at the vertex of a small square in the drawing.51. What will be the area, in square feet, of Harold's garden?", "choices": {"A": "40", "B": "64", "C": "80", "D": "128", "E": "160"}, "correct": "E"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "52. Use the following information to answer questions 50-52.Harold is planning a garden as shown in the scale drawing below. The line segments represent the fence surrounding the garden, with an opening in the fence to access the garden. Each small square in the scale drawing represents a square with a side length of 2 feet. Each marked point is at the vertex of a small square in the drawing.52. What is the measure of the angle labeled \u03b8 in the scale drawing of the garden?", "choices": {"A": "", "B": "", "C": "", "D": "", "E": ""}, "correct": "E"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "53. What is the solution of the equation  ?", "choices": {"A": "0", "B": "", "C": "2", "D": "4", "E": "7"}, "correct": "D"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "54. For the functions f(x) = 4x + 12 and g(x) = , what is the set of real numbers x on which g(f(x)) is defined?", "choices": {"A": "All real numbers", "B": "All real numbers except 3", "C": "All real numbers except 0", "D": "All real numbers except ", "E": "All real numbers except -3"}, "correct": "E"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "55. One alarm beeps 4 seconds after it is activated and at the end of every 6 seconds after that. Another alarm beeps 29 seconds after it is activated and at the end of every 30 seconds after that. The 2 alarms are activated at the same time and are left on for t minutes, where t is a whole number. What is the total number of times the 2 alarms beep in those t minutes?", "choices": {"A": "12t", "B": "18t", "C": "24t", "D": "60t", "E": "180t"}, "correct": "A"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "56. The inequality 3x4y &lt; 0 is true for real numbers x and y. If it can be determined, which of the following inequalities must be true?", "choices": {"A": "x \uff1c 0", "B": "x \uff1e 0", "C": "y \uff1c 0", "D": "y \uff1e 0", "E": "Cannot be determined from the given information"}, "correct": "C"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "57. In the figure shown below, square MNPT is inscribed in square ABCD. The length of DC is x inches, and the length of BN is y inches. In terms of x and y, which of the following expressions gives the area, in square inches, of MVPT?", "choices": {"A": "x2 - y2", "B": "x2 + y2", "C": "xy - y2", "D": "x2 - 2xy + y2", "E": "x2 - 2xy + 2y2"}, "correct": "E"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "58. For all distinct nonzero values of x and y, which of the following expressions is equivalent to  ?", "choices": {"A": "1", "B": "x", "C": "", "D": "", "E": ""}, "correct": "B"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "59. For 0\u00b0 \uff1c a\u00b0 \uff1c 90\u00b0 and 0 \uff1c b \uff1c 1, when cos a\u00b0 = b, which of the following expressions is equivalent to cos(2a\u00b0) ?(Note: cos 2\u03b8 = (cos \u03b8)2 - (sin \u03b8)2)", "choices": {"A": "-1", "B": "0", "C": "1", "D": "b2 - a2", "E": "2b2 - 1"}, "correct": "E"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "60. In the figure shown below, each of the points labeled P through X is a point of tangency between 2 circles. Each vertex of \u25b3ABC is the center of a circle. Each circle has a radius of r cm. Which of the following expressions represents the area, in square centimeters, of \u25b3ABC?", "choices": {"A": "", "B": "", "C": "", "D": "", "E": ""}, "correct": "A"}]}